Murray Forman Collection of Hip Hop Magazines, 1978-2007 SC 139
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 1. Magazines, 1989-2006; 16 Boxes
  - Rap Sheet (vol. 2, no. 10), 1994 October (Box 8)
    Comin' from the Westside: More Than G-Funk, Above the Law, Black Owned (Paris and Scarface Records, Death Row Records), A Day in San Diego's Hood with Jayo Felony.
  - Rap Sheet (vol. 2, no. 11), 1994 November (Box 8)
    It Ain't About the Coasts, Chicago's Common Sense, Arrested Development, Around the Hip Hop Nation, Black Owned (Jermain Dupri's So So Def label).
  - Rap Sheet (vol. 2, no. 12), 1994 December (Box 8)
    Lords of the Underground
    Underground Funk, Lords of the Underground, Too Short, Oakland Funk, State of Emergency (L.A. Riots of '92), Redman's Darkside, Scarface's Diary.
  - Rap Sheet (vol. 3, no. 2), 1995 February (Box 8)
    Naughty by Nature
    Special Report: Violence in Hip Hop (the artist's side of the story), Digable Planets, Naughty by Nature, Dancehall and hip hop, Black Owned (Sean "Puffy" Combs and Bad Boy Entertainment).
  - Rap Sheet (vol. 3, no. 3), 1995 March (Box 8)
    Def Squad
    Slick Rick speaks from behind bars, Erick Sermon and Def Squad, Black on the Rise is the Planet Brooklyn, Day in the Hood (Tootsee-Rollin' through Jacksonville, Florida with the 69 Boyz).
  - Rap Sheet (vol. 3, no. 4), 1995 April (Box 8)
    Special Report: Republicans and Rap, Ol' Dirty Bastard from the Wu-Tang Clan.
  - Rap Sheet (vol. 3, no. 5), 1995 May (Box 8)
    Special Report: 3rd Anniversry of the L.A. Riots, Amerikkka's most wanted film maker (Ice Cube), Ace in the Hole (Masta Ace), hip-hop's true Muslim soldier (KAM's Made in America), Violence in hip-hop part 3, Day in the Hood (Atlanta's Ichiban Records, Nefertiti), Phill Most, the Soulman.
  - Rap Sheet (vol. 3, no. 8), 1995 August (Box 8)
    Cypress Hill
    HIV & the hip hop generation part 2, Hip hop & sports, Cypress Hill, Priority Records 10th anniversary, St. Ides: Ad-ventures in commercial rap (malt liquor's aggressive community marketing), RBL Posse, Bay area's underground, D&D Project.
  - Rap Sheet (vol. 4, no. 10), 1996 October (Box 8)
    MC Lyte
    Above the Law, MC Lyte, Outkast, Dru Down, The Iron Man (Ghost Face Killah), The Roots, Chelby Harris, Sugar Hill Gang.
  - Rap Sheet (vol. 4, no. 11), 1996 November (Box 8)
    Tupac Shakur
    Mr. Mike representing for the Dirty South, Tupac's divided soul, Jeru the Damaja, Whodini, Day in the Hood (Richie Rich debuts another side of Oakland), DJ Jus and Lil' Nique.
  - Rolling Stone, 1990 August 9 (Box 9)
    Julia Roberts
    2 Live Crew Fighting Back (article on their obscenity battle in court).
  - Rolling Stone, 1990 September 6 (Box 9)
    M.C. Hammer
    M.C. Hammer, Living Colour.
  - Rolling Stone, 1990 October 4 (Box 9)
    The Women of Twin Peaks
    College Special, Ice Cube, Stevie Ray Vaughan tribute.
  - Rolling Stone, 1990 November 15 (Box 9)
    Bruce Springsteen
    Special Issue: The 80s, Kings of Rap with Russell Simmons and Rick Rubin, Artists' Choice featuring Chuck D.
  - Rolling Stone, 1993 September 30 (Box 9)
    Dr. Dre and Snoop Doggy Dogg
    Dr. Dre and Snoop Dogg, Rock & Rap Will Stand (about Judgement Night soundtrack featuring Cypress Hill, Helmet, and Ice-T).
  - Rolling Stone, 1994 June 2 (Box 9)
    Kurt Cobain
    Kurt Cobain tribute issue, Beastie Boys, Spike Lee.
  - Rolling Stone, 1996 April 4 (Box 9)
    Sean Penn
    Snoop Doggy Dogg beats murder rap.
  - Rolling Stone, 1997 April 17 (Box 9)
    Beck
    Notorious B.I.G. 1973-1997 tribute.
  - Rolling Stone, 1997 October 16 (Box 9)
    Salt-n-Pepa, Wu-Tang Clan, Ray Charles.
  - Rolling Stone, 1998 October 29 (Box 9)
    Hip-Hop Now: The Top 50 Players (Master P, Wyclef Jean, Jay-Z)
    Hip-Hop 1998.
  - Rolling Stone, 2003 July 24 (Box 9)
    Eminem
    The Genius of Eminem, Rap's Mix Masters, Macy Gray, Beyonce, James Brown at Bonnaroo.
  - Rolling Stone, 2006 November 16 (Box 9)
    Jon Stewart & Stephen Colbert
    Hip-Hop Report: Jay-Z, Nas, Diddy, Young Jeezy, Tupac, The marketing of Jay-Z.
  - The Source (vol. 3, no. 4), 1990 Summer (Box 10)
  - The Source (vol. 1, no. 5) [sic], 1990 October (Box 10)
    LL Cool J
  - The Source (no. 16), 1990 December (Box 10)
    Eazy E: The Gangsta Rapper
  - The Source (no. 17), 1991 January (Box 10)
    2 Live Crew's Luther Campbell
  - The Source (no. 19), 1991 March/April (Box 10)
    Paris, Lakim Shabazz, and Big Daddy Kane: An Islamic Summit
  - The Source (no. 20), 1991 May (Box 10)
    Ice T: Hip-Hop goes Hollywood
  - The Source (no. 21), 1991 June (Box 10)
    De La Soul: "The Death of the Daisy Age"
  - The Source (no. 23), 1991 August (Box 10)
    Heavy D
  - The Source (no. 24), 1991 September (Box 10)
  - The Source (no. 25), 1991 October (Box 10)
  - The Source (no. 33), 1992 June (Box 10)
    TLC
  - The Source (no. 35), 1992 August (Box 10)
    Too $hort
  - The Source (no. 36), 1992 September (Box 10)
    EPMD & The Hit Squad
  - The Source (no. 37), 1992 October (Box 10)
  - The Source (no. 38), 1992 November (Box 10)
    Dr. Dre
  - The Source (no. 39), 1992 December (Box 10)
    Spike Lee and Charles Barkley
  - The Source (no. 41), 1993 February (Box 10)
    Run DMC
  - The Source (no. 44), 1993 May (Box 10)
  - The Source (no. 45), 1993 June (Box 10)
    Onyx
  - The Source (no. 49), 1993 October (Box 10)
    Kriss Kross
  - The Source (no. 50), 1993 November (Box 10)
    Grandmaster Flash, Afrika Bambaataa, Kool DJ Herc: Hip-Hop History
  - The Source (no. 52), 1994 January (Box 10)
    Das EFX
  - The Source (no. 53), 1994 February (Box 10)
  - The Source (no. 54), 1994 March (Box 11)
    Record label owner Luther Campbell, aka "Luke"
  - The Source (no. 55), 1994 April (Box 11)
    GangStarr
  - The Source (no. 56), 1994 May (Box 11)
  - The Source (no. 57), 1994 June (Box 11)
    Scarface: MC Eiht & Spice 1 Defend Reality Rap
  - The Source (no. 58), 1994 July (Box 11)
  - The Source (no. 59), 1994 August (Box 11)
    Flavor Flav
  - The Source (no. 61), 1994 October (Box 11)
    Coolio
  - The Source (no. 62), 1994 November (Box 11)
  - The Source (no. 63), 1994 December (Box 11)
  - The Source (no. 64), 1995 January (Box 11)
    Mary J. Blige - Queen of Ghetto Love!
  - The Source (no. 65), 1995 February (Box 11)
    MC Eiht
  - The Source (no. 66), 1995 March (Box 11)
    Slick Rick
  - The Source (no. 67), 1995 April (Box 11)
    Naughty By Nature
  - The Source (no. 68), 1995 May (Box 11)
    Death Row: New Players in the Game (Nate Dogg, Daz, Jewell and Kurupt)
  - The Source (no. 69), 1995 June (Box 11)
    Eazy-E (memorial issue)
  - The Source (no. 70), 1995 August (Box 11)
    Bone Thugs-n-Harmony
  - The Source (no. 73), 1995 October (Box 11)
    The Wu-Tang Empire Shines!: Method Man, Raekwon, & the RZA
  - The Source (no. 74), 1995 November (Box 11)
    Erick Sermon
  - The Source (no. 75), 1995 December (Box 11)
    Ladies Love Cool J (featuring LL Cool J)
  - The Source (no. 76), 1996 January (Box 12)
    The Year in Hip-Hop '95 (Snoop, Mobb Deep, LL Cool J, E-40, Raekwon & Ghostface, Tupac, and more)
  - The Source (no. 77), 1996 February (Box 12)
  - The Source (no. 78), 1996 March (Box 12)
    Tupac Free?
  - The Source (no. 79), 1996 April (Box 12)
    Ice T: Putting the Freeze on Gang Warfare
  - The Source (no. 80), 1996 May (Box 12)
    Ice Cube: East vs. West, Inside Hip-Hop's Civil War
  - The Source (no. 81), 1996 June (Box 12)
  - The Source (no. 82), 1996 July (Box 12)
    Dr. Dre Leaves Death Row
  - The Source (no. 83), 1996 August (Box 12)
    The Year 2000: A Look Into the Future of the Hip-Hop Generation (featuring Nas)
  - The Source (no. 84), 1996 September (Box 12)
    Suge Knight
  - The Source (no. 85), 1996 October (Box 12)
    Da Brat
  - The Source (no. 87), 1996 December (Box 12)
    Snoop Doggy Dogg: The Death and Rebirth of G-Funk
  - The Source (no. 88), 1997 January (Box 12)
    The Power and the Players of '96
  - The Source (no. 91), 1997 April (Box 12)
  - Spice, 1990 June (Box 13)
    Biz Markie, Salt-N-Pepa, Sweet Tee, Ice-T, De La Soul, Queen Latifah, Digital Underground, Young MC, Rob Base, Wrecks'n'Effect, Redhead Kingpin, Troop, Jazzie B., Chimes, Technotronic, 3rd Bass, Good Girls.
  - Spice, 1990 August (Box 13)
    Ice Cube, Tianamen Square, Oran "Juice" Jones, Boogie Down Productions, Bell Biv Devoe, Tribe Called Quest, Big Lady K, Mark Dee, Kool Moe Dee, Tony Toni Tone!, Low Profile, Jeff Redd, Too Short, Boo-Yaa T.R.I.B.E., Tyler Collins, Young and Restless, X-Clan.
  - Spice, 1990 October (Box 13)
    Eric B. & Rakim, Cameo, Groove B Chill, Chubb Rock, Special Ed, LL Cool J, Tairrie B., Master Ace, M.C. Shan, Public Enemy, Poor Righteous Teachers, Johnny Gill, Milira, Rebel MC.
  - Spin (vol. 5, no. 6), 1989 September (Box 13)
    Natalie Merchant
    Al Sharpton, N.W.A., Exposé, LL Cool J, Professor Griff.
  - Spin (vol. 6, no. 1), 1990 April (Box 13)
    Sinead O'Connor
    N.W.A., Professor Griff, Screamin' Jay Hawkins.
  - Spin (vol. 6, no. 3), 1990 June (Box 13)
    Lisa Stansfield
    Hip Hop Map of America, Ditch Them Dirty Discs, Delta Blues.
  - Spin (vol. 6, no. 6), 1990 September (Box 13)
    Billy Idol
    2 Live Crew.
  - Spin (vol. 6, no. 7), 1990 October (Box 13)
    Spike Lee (guest editor)
    Eddie Murphy, Al Sharpton, New Black Cinema, Living Colour, Marion S. Barry, 2 Live Crew, Bad Brains, Public Enemy, Joie De Lee, race.
  - Spin (vol. 6, no. 8), 1990 November (Box 13)
    Jon Bon Jovi
    Censorship Isn't Def American (Geto Boys).
  - Spin (vol. 7, no. 4), 1991 July (Box 13)
    Fishbone, Massive Attack, John Robie.
  - Spin (vol. 7, no. 6), 1991 September (Box 13)
    Prince
    Yo! MTV Unwrapped, N.W.A., 3rd Bass, Dreaming America (hip hop criticism).
  - Spin (vol. 8, no. 1) (Special 7th Anniversary Issue), 1992 April (Box 13)
    Seven Greatest Bands of All Time (includes Public Enemy, Jimi Hendrix).
  - Spin (vol. 8, no. 7), 1992 October (Box 13)
    Chuck D and Hank Shocklee
    Public Enemy, MC Serch and Chubb Rock, Sister Souljah, "reaming America (America's musical color line, segregation in the music industry)".
  - Spin (vol. 10, no. 5), 1994 August (Box 13)
    Perry Farrell
    The Big Mack (Suge Knight).
  - Spin (vol. 16, no. 8), 2000 August (Box 13)
    Marshall Mathers
  - Street Sound (no. 56), 1992 April (Box 14)
    Super Cat
    Special Report: Reggae Big n' Ready.
  - Street Sound (no. 63), 1993 March (Box 14)
    Brand Nubian
  - Stress (no. 22), 1999 December (Box 14)
    The Lox
    The Lox, DJ Kay Slay, Pharoahe Monch.
  - Time (vol. 153, no. 5), 2000 February (Box 14)
    Hip Hop Nation
  - True (no. 5), 2004 Fall (Box 14)
    Queen Pen, Method Man, DJ 3rd Eye, Funky Fresh Records, MC Spice, Bass Blak, Jim Jones.
  - True (no. 6), 2005 Winter (Box 14)
    Slim Thug, Fabolous
    Fabolous, Guerilla Black, Ja Rule, Jacki-O, Paul Wall, De La Soul, Royce 5'9.
  - True (no. 7), 2005 Summer (Box 14)
    Mike Jones, The Birdman
    Mike Jones, JT Money, Big Noyd, Venom Entertainment, Rebirth of New England Hip Hop, Boston's Big Bounce Dance Competition, 50 Cent, Birdman, Lil' Kim, Tweet, 112, Baby Williams, JR Writer.
  - Up Front (no. 24), 1993 January (Box 14)
    Bell Biv Devoe, Brand Nubian, Dance Music, Segregation in the Top 40, To Kill a Cop: The New Politics of Rap?
  - Urb (vol. 47), 1996 April (Box 14)
    Fugees
  - Word Up (vol. 3, no. 6), 1990 June (Box 14)
    Salt 'n' Pepa, Queen Latifah, Kid 'n Play, Janet Jackson, Public Enemy, Big Daddy Kane, Heavy D. & Hakeem, MC Lyte.
    House-Rap Mixture, Bobby Brown, DJ Doc.
  - Word Up (vol. 4, no. 4), 1991 February (Box 14)
    LL Cool J, Run-DMC, En Vogue, Big Daddy Kane, Kool G. Rap & DJ Polo.
    MC Trouble, Nikki D, Dana Dane, EPMD, Rakim, Doug E. Fresh, Troop, Al B. Sure.
  - WYWS (While You Were Sleeping), 2006 (Box 14)
  - YSB (vol. 2, no. 4), 1993 January (Box 14)
    LL Cool J, KRS-One, Portrait, Chubb Rock, Homelessness.
  - XXL, 1997 August (Box 15)
  - XXL, 1998 March (Box 15)
    D'Angelo
  - XXL, 1998 May (Box 15)
    R. Kelly
  - XXL, 1999 April (Box 15)
    Nas
  - XXL, 2000 July (Box 15)
    Snoop Dogg
  - XXL, 2000 August (Box 15)
  - XXL, 2002 January/February (Box 15)
  - XXL, 2002 May (Box 15)
    Crooked I, N.I.N.A., Simon, Kurupt, Eastwood (We Thuggin': Suge Knight and His New Heavy Hitters.)
  - XXL, 2002 December (Box 15)
  - XXL, 2003 January/February (Box 15)
    Bravehearts Wiz, Nas, God's Son, Jungle
  - XXL, 2003 August (Box 15)
    50 Cent
  - XXL, 2003 October (Box 15)
    Afeni Shakur (mother of 2Pac)
  - XXL, 2003 November (Box 16)
    Outkast's Andre 3000
  - XXL, 2003 December (Box 16)
  - XXL, 2004 March (Box 16)
  - XXL, 2004 June (Box 16)
    Shyne
  - XXL, 2005 January/February (Box 16)
  - XXL, 2005 March (Box 16)
  - XXL, 2005 August (Box 16)
    Jay-Z, Kanye West, Lebron James, Foxy Brown
  - XXL, 2005 September (Box 16)
    The Game
  - XXL, 2006 November (Box 16)
- 2. Articles, 1978-2000; 2 Boxes
  - Billboard Magazine Chart Ratings, 1978-1992; 1 Folder (Box 17)
  - Billboard Magazine Chart Ratings, 1993-1998; 1 Folder (Box 18)
  - Billboard Magazine, Misc. Articles, 1996-2000; 1 Folder (Box 18)
  - Esquire article, "Gangsta Life, Gangster Death" (about Tupac Shakur), 1996 December; 1 Folder (Box 18)
  - Clippings about rap film "Black and White", 2000; 1 Folder (Box 18)
  - Clippings about Chuck D and Notorius B.I.G., 1997/1999; 1 Folder (Box 18)
- 3. Interview, 2007; 1 Audio File digital
  - Fernando Orejuela interview with Murray Forman for AAAMC Liner Notes, no. 12 (Winter 2007), July 30, 2007; DAF 238; 1 Audio File (1 hr., 8 min., 40 sec.): stereo; 32-bit/8 kHz, 6.38 MB + transcript (21 pages) (Box 18)
    Online Streaming in Media Collections Online
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/v73b98nk80